http://www.firsttryon.com/privacy-policy

What We DoAdvisory ServicesSales and TradingWho We AreOur HistoryOur MissionOur ProfessionalsOur Involvement in the CommunityNewsCareersContact Us
Privacy Policy
First Tryon Privacy Policy Thank you for visiting First Tryon. Your privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting and safeguarding the privacy of our customers, employees, job applicants and visitors to our web sites who provide personal information. Personal information is defined as any information concerning the personal or material circumstances of an identified or identifiable individual. Personal information shall include, but is not limited to name, home address, home zip code, telephone numbers, email addresses and employment related information such as may be found on résumés, applications, background verification information, or in employment references.
This Privacy Policy applies to information gathered by First Tryon, including through this site, wwwfirsttryon.com, and all sites of the affiliates of First Tryon that are linked to this site (collectively, the "Sites"). By viewing or using any Site, by submitting personal information, and/or by accessing and using any Site, you are agreeing to our data collection and use practices and other terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy and as otherwise required by law. Information We Collect It is First Tryon policy to maintain all personal information as confidential. First Tryon only gathers personal information, such as, first and last names, phone numbers, addresses and email addresses, when voluntarily submitted by you. For example, personal information may be collected from you in order to get your feedback on our Sites or apply for a job with First Tryon. How We Use and Retain Your Information In addition to consenting to the Privacy Policy and the terms and conditions, you expressly consent that First Tryon may share the information that you have provided within the First Tryon family as discussed herein. The First Tryon family includes our subsidiaries, affiliates and those companies engaged to perform functions such as providing technical assistance for our Sites and our business operations. First Tryon does not sell, rent or otherwise distribute to third parties personal information about visitors to the Sites, except as needed for First Tryon to provide the services for which such information was volunteered. It is First Tryon's policy to keep personal information only for as long as needed for such purposes. First Tryon reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the Sites, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety. How to Access and Update Your Information If at any time, you would like to review, correct or delete the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us or on behalf of our business partners, you can let us know by logging into your account on the Sites or by contacting us. How We Secure Your Information Securing your information is a company priority and we take all reasonable steps to prevent unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information. We use industry standard security measures to help protect the confidentiality of personal information. Your account information is protected by the password you use to access your online account. Please keep this password confidential. When you apply for a position with First Tryon, your personal information is encrypted and stored on secured servers. Personal information that is maintained in our offices is subject to physical, administrative and technical controls as well. Hard copies of sensitive personal information are maintained in locked locations or cabinets with similar restrictions for electronic storage. When disposed of, the information is shredded, destroyed, erased, or otherwise sought to be made unreadable. Electronic Notice if Security Breach If we are required to provide notice of unauthorized access of certain security systems, you agree that we may do so when required or voluntarily by posting notice on the Sites or sending notice to any email address we have for you, in the good faith discretion of First Tryon. You agree that notice to you will count as notice to any other individual for whom you are acting and agree to provide the notice to any such individual. Cookies "Cookies" are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Some of the Sites may collect page session cookie information to allow for a better page experience during use, however, no personal information is stored and we do not use "Cookies" for tracking purposes. Links to Other Sites We may offer links to sites that are not operated by First Tryon. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies, and any information you submit to those companies is subject to their privacy policies. First Tryon’ Websites The Sites operated by First Tryon will adhere to this Privacy Policy. Given the global nature of both the Internet and First Tryon, using the Internet to collect and process personal information usually involves the transmission of data on an international basis. By browsing the Sites and communicating electronically with us, you agree that we may export personal information to one or more of our offices in other countries and process it there in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Although data may be held in countries that do not have strict data privacy laws, we do take steps to maintain the privacy and security of your personal information. First Tryon' privacy practices are consistent with the European Union Data Protection Directive and the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. Changes to our Privacy Policy First Tryon reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy from time to time. We suggest that you check here periodically for the most up-to-date version of our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept those changes. Contact Us Please feel free to contact the Compliance Officer with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the protections of your information. You may also contact the Compliance Officer to remove your personal information from First Tryon.
1355 Greenwood Cliff Rd #401 Charlotte, NC 28204 (704) 926-2445
